{
    "id": "1e6c2314c45044a7b9798e33767a1665",
    "title": "Verb Forms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It was John who …………………… the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "alert",
                "alerts",
                "alerted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f686989b0bda412b9483f13fa9cb9599"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………….. for ages.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are waiting",
                "have been waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f4a4144c8399427da3488ee0df1e84df"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. her for a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "have known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "26ea3261f2f34cf8b93dc6b6d6b90e0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The box …………………… so heavy that I could not lift it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has been",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "329e4f890952446dbe32b0cd42891d86"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of my friends ………………… to Zambia recently.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has gone",
                "went",
                "goes"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c7a6f74f379a4c3b89dfd48ee9cf48aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………… a novel since October, and now he is about to finish it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was writing",
                "has been writing",
                "is writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a5fb81cf0604d979718f201e5523229"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call you when the guests ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will arrive",
                "would arrive",
                "arrive"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c5b4954769e84b7eab7c7b2352597d8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Age and experience ................................ wisdom to man.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bring",
                "brings",
                "brought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ec9bbd66dd0b4678a3a058007f502465"
        },
        {
            "question": "The prize was ........................... away by our team.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "borne",
                "born",
                "bore"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "585118b836c3478297d83220f82bf872"
        },
        {
            "question": "They were ................................ questioned.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been",
                "being",
                "be"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "05226d9339994a21b740f866d57c381a"
        }
    ]
}